Next notice
We're here! We're here!
Karuizawa! It's Karuizawa!
Karuizawa? Where is it?
What? Where is it?
I don't know.
Ura!
It's been like this today.
This is how we're going to do it today.
I'm going to keep doing it like this.
If you like...
I hope you'll feel like you're on a trip of a lifetime.
Today, we're going to have a party in the streets of Karuizawa.
Matching things?
Yes!
A trip to find matching things! I'm sure there are lots of stores to choose from.
I can already see them. Yes! It was awesome on the way here. It was awesome!
Okay, you guys, let's take a trip... together! Okay, let's go! Let's go!
But it's so nice today, and it's so cool on this side of the country.
That's great! It's really cool! I want to stay here forever!
Go to Karuizawa in the summer!
I haven't been here all summer! What's going on? I can't find Mojiko and Nanaka! Just when I thought "What's going on?
I'm going to Karuizawa! I'm off to Karuizawa! You can be in Karuizawa!
What?
What do you mean?
It's different.
A little bit? Sort of. A little bit? I don't know.
That's great. That's something.
Oh, okay.
Where do you want me to put my hand?
Right here.
Oh, okay.
I'm looking forward to this.
Risa's been dancing for you.
Thank you, Nanisa.
You should join us, too.
I'm so embarrassed.
Well...
What should I do with this? Don't be embarrassed.
It's nice.
I'm scared.
Moeza and Shichirisa.
Where do you want to go now?
We've walked a bit. It's getting hot.
I'm starting to feel like having a cold one.
What would you like?
Looks delicious!
Berries, Haskap, ice cream...
Ice cream!
Wet rice crackers! Wet rice crackers!
I love wet rice crackers!
I want some wet rice crackers.
Want some?Want some?
Here it is.
Up, up!
Let's eat.
I'll have a rice cracker.
Try it.
Tasty?
It's not a Miu-Len-On-Kakki, it's a Sen.
Yes, it's good.
Wait a minute.
You saw me while you were at it.
Did you?
I'm here!
You got it?
Barley tea. It's delicious.
It's delicious.
It's like it's completely off, now.
It's a little... I don't know if it's safe to be this loose.
Where are you?
How's the barley tea commercial going?
Kalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanchalanch.
Mugi-cha (barley tea)
Ha-ha-ha.
Scroll down to the end of my life.
I'd like to fast forward to here.
Please continue!
Japanese Culture
Hey.Hey. Hey.
What are you doing? I'm going to go eat.
Oh, there it is. There it is.
Oh, my God.
I've got Beulah's burns.
What's with the kitty balls?
I'm curious.
What cat's balls?
How cute!
There's also a fortune stone.
Look at the cat!
What a cute face!
There it is!
Kyoton-neko!
Yeah, cute!
It's a deep sea blue, a dragonfly damselfly.
So, there were a lot of cute ones.
No, no, no, I couldn't find any.
I couldn't find one that matched.
I made them matching.
What was it, white?
White.
Cats?
Cats white.
Cats white?Cats white?
White Cats is white white.
Cats white.
Cat's White... it's really easy to forget.
Cat's White bracelet.
It's cute, a little white, and elegant.
It's a little white and classy.
Would you like to wear it?
Let's do it now!
After you.
I'll put it on myself.
I'll do it.
We're independent.
I'll put it on.
I'll do it myself.
Earlier, I asked if we could put them on each other.
Yes, I can put them on.
Yes, I can.
Yes, I did.
You thought we'd stick them together.
You thought we would.
You're not going to do it today?
We did it ourselves.
You thought we did, but we didn't.
I see... let's go next time.
Let's do that.
Now, now, let's have something cold this time.
Ice cream, honey ice cream, honey ice cream, honey ice cream. It's honey ice cream, honey ice cream, honey ice cream.
Bee s'mores ice cream.
Honey ice cream with honey. One ice cream with honey on it.
500 yen.
Thank you! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Look at all this honey!
Shall we eat?
Let's eat.
I got the part with honey on it. - No honey on it?
I'll eat it.
I'll take some too.
Okay, ready?
Yummy, yummy, yummy! Honey!
What's this? It's coming from the weirdest place!
It's coming from the weirdest place!
And we also got a drink. It's a plum drink.
It's a plum drink... plum and honey, so I guess that means it's dipped in plum.
I'll try it.
It's so good! I'll drink it.
This is my throw. That's it. That's it.
Don't turn it. Okay.
It's so cool that you wrote your name on it.
He wrote his name on it.
I wrote my name on it.
I want to drink it every day this season.
I want to make it a staple.
I'll try it. I'll try it. I'll try it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Rabbit.
It's funny.
Oops, not cute. Not even remotely exciting.
Why did I get in? You bent it too much.
That's what I mean. A little bend.
A little bend.
Wait a minute... you know what he said...
Like a cup!
It's not a cup.
It's funny
That was funny.
It's funny.
He went wan, wan, wan. He was everywhere.
I say "wan, wan, wan." Maybe it's "tense wan, wan, wan.
No, no, no.
I lost my chopsticks the other day.
Yes, the film on the top.
Let's look at the chopsticks. I want those.
Like cute chopstick rests.
Really? Wow, there must be some unusual designs.
You were looking at them while you ate?
I kept looking at the big shoes.
We went to a chopstick shop.
Yes, yes, a chopstick shop.
I thought the chopstick container was cute.
I didn't expect that. No way.
Oh, no!
Matching goods
Spenlight-colored
Oh, yeah, that's not so bad.
Unexpected
I bought a matching set that I didn't expect.
This one is yellow and this one is yellow and green
yellow and green
Yellow and green teacups
Red and light blue teacups
And these are microwave-safe and dishwasher-safe.
And you can put them in the dishwasher.
That's amazing!
It's amazing!
Delicious miso soup and
I'd like to put
I want to put it in and eat it.
I'd like to eat it.
I bought some chopstick containers and some souvenirs for the members.
I bought some souvenirs.
I also want to buy some souvenirs for the members.
I want to buy souvenirs for the members.
So...
I'd like to take a look.
I'll take a look.
Yay!
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
So...
Karuizawa
Prince
Karuizawa Prince Shopping Plaza
Here we are!
It's a beautiful day.
The vast nature is spreading
A place for shopping
Like an outlet
The trees started to grow.
There was a tree that was about a foot tall
Such a solid
There are so many fun things
There's a lot of fun stuff here.
What is that lawn?
It's like...
I wish I could shop here, too.
I hope to be able to shop here as well.
I hope I can buy something good.
I'm off.
Flowers.
My favorite
Chibaha Kiwawa was there
Chibaha was there
like she was into it just now.Like, I'm into it now.
I'll do the "too much of this" thing.
What was that?
P
Pee.
Cute!
P
So many things
But what's that?
What is that?
I wonder if they have a barbecue?
It's a beautiful day.
I want to argue with the staff.
I caught something
This camera, Chiamura...
I knew he likes me.
That's right.
But I'm sorry.
I don't.
I can't.
I don't think...
You might like it.
Ooh.
Oh!
There are so many amazing admired brands!
I admire Birk
Shall we?Do you want to do it?
I do.
I've been caught
I mean, don't do it, don't do it, don't do it.
I yearn for you, Burke.
I mean, don't do it.
I put it back in.
They put it back in.
Tambo.
Tambo. Tambo.
It's autumn.
Wait, wait, wait, I hate it when you look at me.
I was just wondering what that was about.
Do it again.
I'm so sorry.
I only get one a day.
Why? Why? Why?
I did it!
I found seven dragonflies.
I'm scared.
It's gentle.
It's going for my finger!
Got it!
I stare at my finger
It's been hot all this time
It's so cool, but now it's hot
The store isThe store.
The Gerapis.
It's so cute.
It's like a loungewear.
Shall we go?
Ready?
Come on, come on, come on!
I can't see.
I can see it.
Look at this.
So many!
I bought a lot
I did a lot of shopping.
Good shopping!
There were so many cute clothes
There were kimonos
There were summer clothes, too
It was so hard to decide
We were so serious about our selections that we were surprised.
I don't know how long we went there.
We went so many places.
So we're just going to start right here.
I have to go.
I'm going to take the bullet train.
Oh, God.
I wish I could go on and on, but...I wish I could go on and on, but
I'll have to come back.
Yeah, I know.
So we got to do some shopping.
I got to eat some of the delicious food from the trip.
And I was able to buy this full set.
As it is, I got it right.
I was able to buy it.
I got it.
I'm here.
I can see you.
I'd like to go to the bullet train now.
Closing?
Closing.
How was your trip?
Did you have a nice trip?
It was fun.
Look at that.
It makes me want to go back.
I knew it! I heard it! I'm so happy!
I had a really, really good time.
I hope you guys get to see a lot of it.
See you later.
See you on our holiday.
It's going to be a holiday. A holiday.